YWCA of the U.S.A. Records. Record Group 9. Photographs
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES II. SLIDES
  - Subseries G. Community Associations
    - Puerto Rico (Box 1060, Folder 14)
    - Virginia (Box 1060, Folder 15)
    - Washington (Box 1060, Folder 16)
- SERIES III. FILMSTRIPS
  - Scripts [no surviving filmstrip]
    - "Around the World with the YWCA," 1949 (Box 1061, Folder 1)
    - National Support filmstrip, 1959 (Box 1061, Folder 2)
    - "The Story of Miss 'Y' and the YWCA Retirement Fund," 1965 (Box 1061, Folder 3)
  - Filmstrip: "The House that Y Built," circa 1957 (Box 1061, Folder 4)